[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "You are, as -- as I said at the top of this show, you are a kind of rock star, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "are", ",", "as", "--", "as", "I", "said", "at", "the", "top", "of", "this", "show", ",", "you", "are", "a", "kind", "of", "rock", "star", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "You know, I never think of it that way, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "never", "think", "of", "it", "that", "way", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "What do you call it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "call", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Well, we call it a service.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "call", "it", "a", "service", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Twenty-five minutes?", "question_tokens": ["Twenty-five", "minutes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "So you have a 25 minute address which you memorize, right?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "have", "a", "25", "minute", "address", "which", "you", "memorize", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Do you ever use notes?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "use", "notes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Well, I write -- I type what I'm going to say.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "write", "--", "I", "type", "what", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Why have you emerged as the -- the big telegenic superstar do you think of this genre?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "have", "you", "emerged", "as", "the", "--", "the", "big", "telegenic", "superstar", "do", "you", "think", "of", "this", "genre", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "You know, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "What is the state of America spiritually right now, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "state", "of", "America", "spiritually", "right", "now", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "Well, I'm an optimist.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "an", "optimist", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "What do you think is the reality?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "is", "the", "reality", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "You know, I see it both ways.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "see", "it", "both", "ways", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "IN", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ":", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ":", "IN", "VB", "RB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "Do you feel that America needs to change its direction?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "that", "America", "needs", "to", "change", "its", "direction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "I think in -- in one sense that we do need to change in -- like has been talked about a lot now -- to let go a little bit of the anger.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "in", "--", "in", "one", "sense", "that", "we", "do", "need", "to", "change", "in", "--", "like", "has", "been", "talked", "about", "a", "lot", "now", "--", "to", "let", "go", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "the", "anger", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "Something that's supposed to bring you hope and harmony and peace often has a completely direct affect, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Something", "that", "'s", "supposed", "to", "bring", "you", "hope", "and", "harmony", "and", "peace", "often", "has", "a", "completely", "direct", "affect", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "It does.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Do you try and calm people down?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "try", "and", "calm", "people", "down", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "RB", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "What do you do as a preacher of such influence?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "do", "as", "a", "preacher", "of", "such", "influence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "You know, my encouragement would always be to obviously not use violence, to be peaceful.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "my", "encouragement", "would", "always", "be", "to", "obviously", "not", "use", "violence", ",", "to", "be", "peaceful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "-- is the way you speak?", "question_tokens": ["--", "is", "the", "way", "you", "speak", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Were you allowed to be a naughty boy, Joel?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "allowed", "to", "be", "a", "naughty", "boy", ",", "Joel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "You know, I didn't -- I never -- I never got off into drugs.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "--", "I", "never", "--", "I", "never", "got", "off", "into", "drugs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joel?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Never tried any of that stuff?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "tried", "any", "of", "that", "stuff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "I never did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "never", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Do you drink?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "drink", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "I never drank.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "never", "drank", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "You never drink alcohol?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "drink", "alcohol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Still don't.", "answer_tokens": ["Still", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Never had a drop?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "had", "a", "drop", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "Never had.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "had", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Not even a tiny, little drop?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "even", "a", "tiny", ",", "little", "drop", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "I think, I --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", ",", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", ":"], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Sneak in the back of the bike shed?", "question_tokens": ["Sneak", "in", "the", "back", "of", "the", "bike", "shed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "You know, one time we would --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "one", "time", "we", "would", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "When your dad wasn't looking, a little drop of cider?", "question_tokens": ["When", "your", "dad", "was", "n't", "looking", ",", "a", "little", "drop", "of", "cider", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", ",", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Do you drink?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "drink", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "You -- you don't smoke?", "question_tokens": ["You", "--", "you", "do", "n't", "smoke", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Never taken drugs?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "taken", "drugs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "No, don't take drugs.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "do", "n't", "take", "drugs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Well, what values did your father instill in you?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "values", "did", "your", "father", "instill", "in", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "I think he instilled in me several.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "instilled", "in", "me", "several", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Or do you believe that some people are simply born evil?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "believe", "that", "some", "people", "are", "simply", "born", "evil", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Well, when you see someone like Adolf Hitler?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "when", "you", "see", "someone", "like", "Adolf", "Hitler", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adolf Hitler"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Was he born evil do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "born", "evil", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "You know, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Do you -- you feel genuine forgiveness towards him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "--", "you", "feel", "genuine", "forgiveness", "towards", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "You know, I may not right now.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "may", "not", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Right now, you find it hard to forgive him?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "now", ",", "you", "find", "it", "hard", "to", "forgive", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "What was the greatest lesson he taught you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "greatest", "lesson", "he", "taught", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "I think the greatest lesson -- well, I think probably the greatest lesson is just to be true to who you are, to follow your own heart.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "greatest", "lesson", "--", "well", ",", "I", "think", "probably", "the", "greatest", "lesson", "is", "just", "to", "be", "true", "to", "who", "you", "are", ",", "to", "follow", "your", "own", "heart", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Did he ever whack you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "ever", "whack", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Do you -- do you -- do you whack your kids?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "--", "do", "you", "--", "do", "you", "whack", "your", "kids", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "We really didn't.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "really", "did", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Never?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "Maybe a couple times.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "a", "couple", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ":"], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "I'm the mean one --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "the", "mean", "one", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "-- when does that fuse finally go?", "question_tokens": ["--", "when", "does", "that", "fuse", "finally", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Well, I've really never seen it go.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "really", "never", "seen", "it", "go", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Victoria"]}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Isn't that unbelievable?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "unbelievable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Come on, Victoria.", "answer_tokens": ["Come", "on", ",", "Victoria", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Isn't that unbelievable?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "unbelievable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "He must have a temper.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "must", "have", "a", "temper", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Like a fist fight?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "a", "fist", "fight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "Never?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "Never have.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "Very competitive.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "competitive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Guilty?", "question_tokens": ["Guilty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "We are guilty.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", "guilty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "CD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "How many books have you sold?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "books", "have", "you", "sold", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "I think I've sold close to 20 million.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "'ve", "sold", "close", "to", "20", "million", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "Twenty million books?", "question_tokens": ["Twenty", "million", "books", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "That's all the by product and all that stuff.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "all", "the", "by", "product", "and", "all", "that", "stuff", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "DVDs?", "question_tokens": ["DVDs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "Well, a lot of those too.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "those", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "How many DVDs?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "DVDs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "I don't even know a figure.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "even", "know", "a", "figure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Do you know how much you're worth?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "much", "you", "'re", "worth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "I never dwell on it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "never", "dwell", "on", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Is it -- is there a contradiction there between saying, you know, \"God wants us all to be rich,\" if actually you're the only rich guy standing there?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "--", "is", "there", "a", "contradiction", "there", "between", "saying", ",", "you", "know", ",", "``", "God", "wants", "us", "all", "to", "be", "rich", ",", "''", "if", "actually", "you", "'re", "the", "only", "rich", "guy", "standing", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "EX", "IN", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "``", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "''", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "Well, again, I don't say that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "again", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "say", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "But do you want me to be rich?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "want", "me", "to", "be", "rich", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "I want you to be rich in health, in relationships.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "want", "you", "to", "be", "rich", "in", "health", ",", "in", "relationships", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "How much do you think I should have?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "do", "you", "think", "I", "should", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "You know, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "And what would you say, Victoria?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "would", "you", "say", ",", "Victoria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Victoria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Could you be happy and poor though, again?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "be", "happy", "and", "poor", "though", ",", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Do you not?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "I am so --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "so", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "Well, let's 20 million books, however many million DVD -- what other income do you have other than those?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "'s", "20", "million", "books", ",", "however", "many", "million", "DVD", "--", "what", "other", "income", "do", "you", "have", "other", "than", "those", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "CD", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "JJ", "CD", "NNP", ":", "WP", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "That's about it.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 646, "question": "And we're talking like tens of millions of dollars, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "we", "'re", "talking", "like", "tens", "of", "millions", "of", "dollars", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 647, "answer": "It's been a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "been", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["tens of millions of dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Do you ever feel guilty?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "feel", "guilty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "I don't ever feel guilty because it comes from -- it's God's blessings on my life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "ever", "feel", "guilty", "because", "it", "comes", "from", "--", "it", "'s", "God", "'s", "blessings", "on", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "And you don't get paid by the church, do you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "do", "n't", "get", "paid", "by", "the", "church", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "You know that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "You've seen the criticism?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "seen", "the", "criticism", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "-- what is wrong with being a prosperity preacher?", "question_tokens": ["--", "what", "is", "wrong", "with", "being", "a", "prosperity", "preacher", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "Well, that's my whole thing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "my", "whole", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 699, "question": "Do you know?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "Oh, our church has raised millions and tens and -- you know, I don't even --", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "our", "church", "has", "raised", "millions", "and", "tens", "and", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "even", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Do -- do you know how much?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "--", "do", "you", "know", "how", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "Have you?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "Which obviously I don't think either of you two were born into great wealth, right?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "obviously", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "either", "of", "you", "two", "were", "born", "into", "great", "wealth", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "CD", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 748, "question": "Is homosexuality a sin, in your eyes?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "homosexuality", "a", "sin", ",", "in", "your", "eyes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 749, "answer": "Yes, I've always believed, Piers, the scripture shows that it's a sin.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'ve", "always", "believed", ",", "Piers", ",", "the", "scripture", "shows", "that", "it", "'s", "a", "sin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "Say, \"Come on, really upset your mother and dad here,\" you know?", "question_tokens": ["Say", ",", "``", "Come", "on", ",", "really", "upset", "your", "mother", "and", "dad", "here", ",", "''", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "``", "NNP", "IN", ",", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "RB", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 773, "question": "The song is on guitar?", "question_tokens": ["The", "song", "is", "on", "guitar", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 775, "question": "What do you -- what do you feel when you watch that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "--", "what", "do", "you", "feel", "when", "you", "watch", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 776, "answer": "You know, I'm so proud.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "so", "proud", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 790, "question": "Which celebrities do you think are good role models?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "celebrities", "do", "you", "think", "are", "good", "role", "models", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 791, "answer": "You know --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 797, "question": "Taylor Swift?", "question_tokens": ["Taylor", "Swift", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 798, "answer": "Yes, she does.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "she", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 818, "question": "What is your -- is homosexuality a sin in your eyes?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "--", "is", "homosexuality", "a", "sin", "in", "your", "eyes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "VBZ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 819, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 843, "question": "So when you see civil partnerships being sanctioned, you think that's wrong, presumably?", "question_tokens": ["So", "when", "you", "see", "civil", "partnerships", "being", "sanctioned", ",", "you", "think", "that", "'s", "wrong", ",", "presumably", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 844, "answer": "Well, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "TO", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 858, "question": "But why are they sinners in your eyes?", "question_tokens": ["But", "why", "are", "they", "sinners", "in", "your", "eyes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 859, "answer": "Well, it's strictly back to what the scripture says.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "strictly", "back", "to", "what", "the", "scripture", "says", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 879, "question": "What would you say to him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 880, "answer": "-- man, I would say \"I love you, Elton John.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "man", ",", "I", "would", "say", "``", "I", "love", "you", ",", "Elton", "John", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "CD", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 894, "question": "Aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 895, "answer": "Well, to me, I just -- I'm not -- I'm not the one to judge and say, you know, who's bad and who's good.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "to", "me", ",", "I", "just", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "the", "one", "to", "judge", "and", "say", ",", "you", "know", ",", "who", "'s", "bad", "and", "who", "'s", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 907, "question": "What do you -- how do they change -- what do they have to do to change to be better people?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "--", "how", "do", "they", "change", "--", "what", "do", "they", "have", "to", "do", "to", "change", "to", "be", "better", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 908, "answer": "Well, I believe it's -- I don't know that I understand it all.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "believe", "it", "'s", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "that", "I", "understand", "it", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 943, "question": "Joel, is it true that you have never had a single date with a woman, or anybody for that matter, until you met Victoria?", "question_tokens": ["Joel", ",", "is", "it", "true", "that", "you", "have", "never", "had", "a", "single", "date", "with", "a", "woman", ",", "or", "anybody", "for", "that", "matter", ",", "until", "you", "met", "Victoria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 944, "answer": "I had not had a formal date.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "not", "had", "a", "formal", "date", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joel"], "LOCATION": ["Victoria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 949, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 950, "answer": "I was busy playing sports.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "busy", "playing", "sports", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 951, "question": "How old were you when you met Victoria?", "question_tokens": ["How", "old", "were", "you", "when", "you", "met", "Victoria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 952, "answer": "I was about 22.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "about", "22", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 953, "question": "ORGAN: So 22 and never been kissed?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "So", "22", "and", "never", "been", "kissed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "CD", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 954, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 960, "question": "Victoria?", "question_tokens": ["Victoria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 961, "answer": "I had opportunity to break him in right.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "opportunity", "to", "break", "him", "in", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 962, "question": "Had you -- had you had boyfriends before?", "question_tokens": ["Had", "you", "--", "had", "you", "had", "boyfriends", "before", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 963, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 969, "question": "So both of -- both of you -- this was the first serious relationship?", "question_tokens": ["So", "both", "of", "--", "both", "of", "you", "--", "this", "was", "the", "first", "serious", "relationship", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "IN", ":", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ":", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 970, "answer": "It was.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 973, "question": "Was it -- was it love at first sight?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "--", "was", "it", "love", "at", "first", "sight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 974, "answer": "I tell people for me it was.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "tell", "people", "for", "me", "it", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 991, "question": "I mean, they have to be pretty strict, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "they", "have", "to", "be", "pretty", "strict", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 992, "answer": "Well, he wasn't a preacher.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "was", "n't", "a", "preacher", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 1002, "question": "That's \"Son of a Preacher Man,\" isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "``", "Son", "of", "a", "Preacher", "Man", ",", "''", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "``", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1003, "answer": "Well, we -- we --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "--", "we", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "IN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 1004, "question": "Were you very chivalrous?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "very", "chivalrous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 1005, "answer": "I don't know what that means.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "that", "means", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 1015, "question": "But are there any annoying aspects to Joel that we should be aware of?", "question_tokens": ["But", "are", "there", "any", "annoying", "aspects", "to", "Joel", "that", "we", "should", "be", "aware", "of", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 1016, "answer": "I know there's --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "there", "'s", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 1019, "question": "-- what -- what annoys you about him?", "question_tokens": ["--", "what", "--", "what", "annoys", "you", "about", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", ":", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1020, "answer": "I'm probably way more spontaneous than he is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "probably", "way", "more", "spontaneous", "than", "he", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", ":", "IN", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1033, "question": "Have you been drinking today?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "been", "drinking", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1034, "answer": "That was -- that was when I was a lot younger.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "--", "that", "was", "when", "I", "was", "a", "lot", "younger", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 1047, "question": "But when you heard him say that, what was your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["But", "when", "you", "heard", "him", "say", "that", ",", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1048, "answer": "I cracked up.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "cracked", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1049, "question": "Did you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1050, "answer": "I thought it was funny.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "it", "was", "funny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", ",", "IN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", ":", "VBG", "TO", ":", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1068, "question": "What's been the single greatest moment of your life outside of marriage and children?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "the", "single", "greatest", "moment", "of", "your", "life", "outside", "of", "marriage", "and", "children", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 1069, "answer": "Outside of marriage and children, outside of knowing the Lord -- coming to -- coming to know the Lord.", "answer_tokens": ["Outside", "of", "marriage", "and", "children", ",", "outside", "of", "knowing", "the", "Lord", "--", "coming", "to", "--", "coming", "to", "know", "the", "Lord", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Compaq Center"]}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 1070, "question": "The -- the moment you'd like to relive again if you had the chance?", "question_tokens": ["The", "--", "the", "moment", "you", "'d", "like", "to", "relive", "again", "if", "you", "had", "the", "chance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1071, "answer": "You know, I think it was an amazing moment when we opened up our new facility, the Compaq Center, where we took the church where my parents had had it for 40 years, and we moved into that premier facility there.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "it", "was", "an", "amazing", "moment", "when", "we", "opened", "up", "our", "new", "facility", ",", "the", "Compaq", "Center", ",", "where", "we", "took", "the", "church", "where", "my", "parents", "had", "had", "it", "for", "40", "years", ",", "and", "we", "moved", "into", "that", "premier", "facility", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 1080, "question": "What would your dad have made of that you think at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "your", "dad", "have", "made", "of", "that", "you", "think", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1081, "answer": "He would be proud.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "would", "be", "proud", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 1101, "question": "Will you feel the same way about meeting me, do you think, Joel?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "feel", "the", "same", "way", "about", "meeting", "me", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "Joel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1102, "answer": "I do even better.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "even", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joel?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1110, "question": "Madonna or Lady Gaga?", "question_tokens": ["Madonna", "or", "Lady", "Gaga", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1111, "answer": "Lady Gaga.", "answer_tokens": ["Lady", "Gaga", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 1129, "question": "How on Earth have you connected to Lady Gaga?", "question_tokens": ["How", "on", "Earth", "have", "you", "connected", "to", "Lady", "Gaga", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1130, "answer": "Oh, not --", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "not", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Earth"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1137, "question": "Simon Cowell -- angel or the devil?", "question_tokens": ["Simon", "Cowell", "--", "angel", "or", "the", "devil", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1138, "answer": "Oh, I think he's an angel.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "an", "angel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1141, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 1142, "answer": "I think -- I think he's -- I think he's smart.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "--", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "smart", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1143, "question": "You both think he's an angel?", "question_tokens": ["You", "both", "think", "he", "'s", "an", "angel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1144, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 1152, "question": "Justin Bieber, cute or annoying?", "question_tokens": ["Justin", "Bieber", ",", "cute", "or", "annoying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 1153, "answer": "Oh, I --", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Justin Bieber"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1164, "question": "Is the death penalty ever justified, and if so, when?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "the", "death", "penalty", "ever", "justified", ",", "and", "if", "so", ",", "when", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 1165, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Osama Bin Laden"]}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 1167, "question": "I struggle with that, you know?", "question_tokens": ["I", "struggle", "with", "that", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 1168, "answer": "If Osama Bin Laden was captured tomorrow --", "answer_tokens": ["If", "Osama", "Bin", "Laden", "was", "captured", "tomorrow", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 1170, "question": "-- should he be executed?", "question_tokens": ["--", "should", "he", "be", "executed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 1171, "answer": "I think that it would probably be a good idea, you know, because of the people they hurt.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "it", "would", "probably", "be", "a", "good", "idea", ",", "you", "know", ",", "because", "of", "the", "people", "they", "hurt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1172, "question": "So execute him?", "question_tokens": ["So", "execute", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1173, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 1174, "question": "Did Michael Vick deserve his second chance?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "Michael", "Vick", "deserve", "his", "second", "chance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1175, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Vick"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 1176, "question": "Do you think everybody does?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "everybody", "does", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 1177, "answer": "I think everybody does.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "everybody", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]